# **Brian Argetsinger**

**Junior Web Developer** 

## **Details**

Address: 2120 Chestnut Street,

Chattanooga, TN Phone: 815-761-9760

Email:

Brian.argetsinger@gmail.com

### Links

LinkedIn GitHub

## **Technical Skills**

HTML CSS JavaScript TypeScript React Angular

# **Professional Summary**

Jr. web developer with a background in operations, retail, and emergency medical services. Each field has been completely different than the last, but has helped my growth as an individual. Bringing forth a motivated attitude and a variety of powerful skills. Committed to utilizing my skills to further the mission of a company.

## **Employment History**

#### Freight & Inventory Associate, Home Depot

Hixon, Jan 2021

- Developed and executed strategy for logistics and inventory management.
- Maintained inventory and ordered supplies as necessary.
- Operator of forklift & other machinery
- Collaborated with other associates for better efficiency

## **Emergency Medical Technician, Amerimed Emergency Services**

Chattanooga, Sep 2019 – Sept 2020

- Maintained assigned ambulance in a state of constant cleanliness and readiness to respond to non-emergency calls.
- Appropriately and safely responded to calls when dispatched.
- Rendered appropriate medical care, within my scope of practice.
- Documented medical histories, concerns, and changes in patient's condition.
- Worked well with nurses, doctors, and medical professionals.
- Helped to maintain meticulous medical records, and made changes when necessary.

#### Shift Manager, Half Price Books

Decatur, Jan 2015 - Sept 2018

- Managed a team of 3-4 booksellers
- Handled cashier duties and money management
- Responsible for buying of new & used merchandise
- Assisted with customer service requests and orders
- Trained over 10 different employees in several different fields

#### **Education**

#### Full Stack Web Developer Certificate, Career Foundry

Aug 2021 - July 2022

- Built a portfolio website from scratch
- Created six separate projects utilizing different builds & programs
- Enhanced skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Angular, Bootstrap, jQuery
- Incorporated back-end testing through Heroku, Firebase, MongoDB
- Constructed serverless functions with test-driven development